CONTACT



+968 97142511



salmaalalawi2011@gmail.co



1134, The Street Oman - Muscat Matrah-Darsit

SKILLS

- MS programmers
- General Computer skills
- Computer language Java, C++, programming C, HTML, CSS, Java script , React ,SQL server
- MVC.NET, Visual studio 2017, Linux.
- Language : Arabic, English, and Hindi.

REFERENCES



Manish Singh Teacher in MCBS 986 94885664 singh.manish.kuma@gmail. com

Salma alalawi

PERSONAL STATEMENT

IT Professional with 5+ years of experience in developing web, batch, and business intelligence solutions for diverse industry clients. Highly instrumental in all phases of the SDLC, with expertise in algorithms and data structures. Successful in developing bespoke solutions, optimizing business procedures, processes, and productivity.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Digital Coin company LLC,

Programmer, November 2019 - March 2023

- Develop React ts front end website .
- Develop and maintain data-centric web applications and services using ASP.NET, C#.NET, MS SQL, and Agile/SCRUM methodologies
- Create and apply UI requirements utilizing MVC.NET, IS/jQuery, HTML, and CSS
- Collaborate with Product Owner and Project Manager to collect requirements and provide implementation
- Develop data-centric web applications and services using Android studio, C#.NET, MS SQL, APIs, and Agile/SCRUM methodologies
- Using Git to share and Merage the team code, Using Jira and bitbucket to manage and check the work.

Almamari Group LLC,

Programmer, Jun 2019 - November 2019

- Develop and maintain data-centric web applications and services using VMware and WordPress .
- Create and manage Employees Email in cPanel and Hosting 24.
- Collaborate with Product Owner and Project Manager to collect requirements and provide implementation
- Collaborate with business analysts, users, and federal agencies to collect requirements and provide implementation

TRAINING EXPERIENCE

Training in Tilal al sad projects and investment L.L.C

The training was for the period of three months, and it was mainly on

- installing and implementing WordPress CMS
- Customize CSS code for word press themes
- Editing WordPress content
- Maintaining custom WordPress plugins.

Training in global computer service L.L.C

The training was for 6 weeks I had the opportunity to learn about development in Microsoft. NET platform .

EDUCATION

- Bachelor's in computer science 2016-2018
- Diploma in ICT 2012-2016

HOBBIES & INTERSTS

- Reading books
- New technology and programmers in mobile computing.